Okay. So, shall we talk about [laughter]
Pam? Get Pam Bondi out of the way, too.
Um, so Pam Bondi goes to she she goes to
Capitol Hill. She's being asked about
the Epstein files. Basically, she didn't
have much to say about him. Um, you
know, my take my answer would have been,
listen, we we released three million of
these things. We said we were going to
do that. I mean, yeah, there's three
more million and yeah, they were
redacted, but that would have been my
talking point. Like, listen, you know,
the Biden people never wanted these out.
We did it. We said we were going to.
Promises made, promises kept would have
been my talking point.
>> Yeah. Yep. Yep.
>> And her talking point was basically,
"Eat [__] [__] you. You're a bunch of
losers. I hate you." And uh and also
your mother's fat and uh and you're gay.
[laughter] So, um it was I mean the the
level of contempt, open contempt on
display. I mean, this this is basically
members of the administration are just
copying Trump, the president's style,
right? I mean, that's basically what it
says.
>> And
oh man, I have so much to say about
this. And everybody gets away with it.
Like, this is what's happened to Decorum
in Washington. And I'm not saying this
is specific to Donald Trump. It's not.
Both sides have just gone over the top.
I I I'm going to take exception with Pam
Bondi's um attitude and behavior. It was
crude. It was rude. It was beneath the
office of uh of the attorney general.
But then at the same time, what the hell
did the Democrats do for four years that
Joe Biden was in the White House and
these three million documents were just
sitting in boxes at the Justice
Department? So, I don't want to hear any
complaints from the likes of Jamie
freaking Raskin.
>> Yeah. What aboutism would have been the
right uh the right talking point?
>> It would have been.
>> I don't understand why she chose not to
go that route. Um, and she, you know,
and she obviously came with pre-armed
talking points. I'm going to say either
directly given to her by the president
or inspired by the president about what
we really should be talking about. Of
course, this has nothing to do with it
is the state of the stock market, the
Dow Jones Industrial Average and all
that. And like look,
>> I mean those numbers are impressive.
Donald Trump has always done well with
the stock market. Uh, he did in his
first term do even when the economy was
a little bit skittish overall. you know,
the the the you know, whatever investors
like him.
>> Yeah, I agree with you.
>> Um Okay. Well, anyway, it was it was a
sight to behold. Um
>> you know, at at first when she just like
started lashing out, I was like, "You've
got to be kidding me. That's what kind
of hearing this is going to be." But
then again, as soon as the Democrats
started talking, I wanted to reach
across the, you know, the the table and
give him a whack across the uh the face
with the back of my hand. Like, where
were you when this information first
came out in 2006?
By the way, also the Democrats don't
ask, and this is really interesting,
what about the other half? We know
you've released half. Um, you know, can
we see the other half? I mean, that's
just being Yeah. Why is that missing in
this discussion? I mean, even among
Epste obsessive people, why do they not
talk about this?
>> Well, as far as the Democrats go,
because they don't really care what's in
the other half. They just want to do
what they can to embarrass the
Republicans,
>> right? Well, the Republicans are doing a
good job at embarrassing
>> They stepped right into it. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean I mean I think
basically this reminds me so much. God,
we keep talking about it's like uh you
know the 60s and the 70s, right? This is
so much like the Watergate tapes like
Yes. You know, I don't want to release
them. I don't want to release them. I'm
not going to release them. You can't
have them. Okay, I'm going to release
them. Well, but I'm going to redact
them. You know, explosive deleted.
Explosive [laughter] deleted.
>> Yeah, exactly. I remember my parents my
parents saying that. I was a little kid.
I was 10 years old when the uh when the
Watergate tapes were released and it was
always exploive redacted, exploive uh
deleted, expletative deleted. And I
remember my mom and dad saying that.
>> That was a big joke.
>> While they were having a conversation
with each other and then they would both
crack up.
>> It was a national joke.
>> Yeah.
>> And and then uh you know [laughter]
and then and then it's like well okay
we're going to get them all and we'll
get them all later. And I mean basically
it's like you know Zeno's paradox right
which is the idea [laughter] that you
can never really cross a room because
you always have to cross half the
remaining distance or you'll never quite
cross the room. I mean obviously paradox
is false but it's sort of like according
to the you know a aerodynamics laws
helicopters can't fly and yet they do.
Um [laughter]
>> that's right but but it's similarly but
it's it's just like that right I mean it
was just sort of like you're just never
getting closer. It reminds me God
there's so many things like that in LA
the metro it inches closer to LAX. It's
never going to quite get to LAX, but I
mean, and it just it just makes it, you
know, rip the band-aid off, Mr.
President, right? Just rip it off. Just
get it over with. Get it put it behind
you.
>> That is right.
>> Um, John from Jennifer Private, do don't
you find it a copout or fault when
Epstein is blamed for on Israel and this
week Russia? All this happened on US
territory and Epstein got a deal from
the US DOJ.
[sighs]
Uh,
>> I don't know. This is complicated.
>> It It's complicated. Listen, I think
this is this is one of those situations
where everybody's guilty. Um, and and I
don't think I don't think anybody's
given anybody a pass. I I believe very
strongly that Epstein was working for
the Israelis. Uh, but now we know from
this latest trunch, he was probably
working for for the Brits and probably
working for the Americans and may have
been working for the Germans. And you
know, he was just one of those guys. So
>> part the worst part about his
unfortunate demise is that we're never
going to get the whole story, are we? I
mean,
>> no. Wouldn't it be great to be able to
interview him?
>> It would be great.
Yeah, it would be great, but it's not
going to happen.
>> I mean, of course, uh, yeah, I won't
make any ridiculous comments about
suicide. Um, okay. [laughter]
Man, do I not believe that. A question
for you, John, from Anak. Why are you so
adamant that Epstein could not have
escaped? Guards and prison officials get
paid off for much less than this kind of
money all the time.
>> No, they don't. And if you have evidence
that they do, present it. But listen,
his brother identified the body. His
brother accompanied the body to the
crematorium for cremation. I think his
brother would recognize him. this AI
picture and video that everybody's
yakking about the last couple of days
that purportedly was in wherever Israel
someplace. It that's all it is. It's
it's AI fantasy.
You have to understand how stupid prison
guards are. They many of them literally
cannot read, let alone implement some
complicated
multiaceted escape for the highest
profile prisoner in the entire federal
system.
>> Yeah. And in a weird way, the
Metropolitan Detention Center has
challenges that like rival Alcatraz in
terms of getting out. You're in the
middle of a densely populated urban area
and it's a highrise. Yeah.
>> Right. I mean, like
>> it is. It's a highrise,
>> right? I mean, so you could think about
all the floors you have to get down. Um,
you know, you can't just go, you know,
climb out the window. It's not I mean,
climb out, if you got out the window,
you're, you know, you're dead anyway.
[music]